I think this is ready.
See if the dough's burnt.
Hey, it's…
SMOKE BILLOWING
It's become crispy like a chip.
Let's just…
A BLACK CHIP?
Let's scrape it off.
Then, it'll be all right.
If we scrape it off
until we see the lighter part…
It's just like brick oven pizza, isn't it?
Brick oven, my foot.
Let's scrape it off.
Geez, he's actually scraping it.
Hey, it looks okay when you scrape it.
Damn it.
PUTS TOPPINGS BACK
I have no choice.
I need to flip and scrape it.
What's that sound?
What? No, it's nothing.
It's going well.
Is there a problem?
No.
DENYING AGAIN
All right.
He's desperately denying any problems.
It's going well.
- Actually, things went as planned.
- Is that so?
Burning it was part of my plan.
I expected it to happen.
- That's a relief then.
- Yeah.
After this, if we reheat it
before serving it,
that will be the cherry on top.
- It worked like a charm.
- This is so funny.
No one will notice.
This… Goodness.
PUTS TOPPINGS BACK AGAIN
I got rid of all the burnt parts though.
ALSO
HE ADDS MORE CHEONGYANG CHILI PEPPERS
Okay.
MEANWHILE, DOWNSTAIRS
THEY DECORATE THE SINK CABINET
DRAWING THE STAFF'S CHARACTERS
KIAN, YEON-KOUNG
ZUHA, JUN-HO
- It's much better.
- Yeah.
- The vibe's a bit more…
- It's brightened up.
This is the golden ratio.
THEY USE THE GOLDEN RATIO
TO MAKE THE WELCOME DRINKS
They'll like it.
Are they arriving soon?
- Ya!
- Hoo!
WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
- Someone's here.
- It must be the guys.
- Ya!
- Hoo!
Do they want us to open up?
- To open the door for them?
- I think so.
NEW GUESTS
Hello.
- What is it?
- It's not them. They're new guests.
- New ones?
- Yes.
- Hello, nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Try opening the door.
- How do we open it?
Open it any way you can.
Just give it a try.
FLUSTERED
- But how?
- Any way you can.
I think they're father and son.
Really?
It seems like a father and son are here.
Really? We should open it for them then.
We should give them the welcome drinks.
It's open.
- Hello!
Welcome.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello, welcome.
- Hello.
Hello. Welcome.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- I'll carry it.
- No, let me.
All right. Thank you.
- Welcome.
First, here are your welcome drinks.
FIRST WELCOME DRINKS WITH NEW RECIPE
- Hello.
- Take a sip first.
GIVE IT A TRY
We mixed lemon juice with water.
Lemon juice?
Thankfully, it's not mono maple sap.
Thank you. I like lemons.
- Please, come on in.
- Yes, come in.
Hello.
- Hello.
Father and son?
FATHER AND SON?
You're not his son?
He's a senior colleague.
I see!
We went to the same high school,
and we're from the same area.
He's my mentor.
I'm majoring in elementary education.
KIM SEONG-JUN
I taught PE.
Now I'm an education supervisor.
LEE SUNG-NAM
- Then, you're a public servant?
- Yes.
You too?
I'm currently studying
as a college student.
- College student?
- Yes.
KNOCKING
- Someone's here.
- Someone else is here.
Be careful.
- Thank you.
- Did you have a good time?
- Hello.
- Yes.
- You look so cold.
THE KOREAN-JAPANESE COUPLE RETURNS
Here are your welcome drinks.
Thank you.
I'm Japanese,
so you can talk to me in Japanese.
Thank you.
- Explain to them, please.
- Yes.
He's the boss.
I'M THE BOSS
JAPANESE MODE TURNS ON
No, I'll just speak Korean.
It's a studio apartment,
like a friend's place.
Like a friend's place,
it's a small studio apartment.
I see.
That's the concept,
and I wanted to make it
as big as possible.
That's why it's huge.
WHEN THE BOSS TALKS, ZUHA TRANSLATES
That's the kitchen and sink.
The kitchen's on the second floor.
There's also a fridge here and a TV there.
Usually, cooking oil and pots
are put in here, right?
OPENING THE SAUNA
It's a sauna.
I thought, "I never imagined this."
I thought it was something
only Kian84 could think of.
5:00 P.M.
- That was fun.
- It was great.
LUGE TEAM & JUN-HO ARE BACK
- They're back.
- Hey, speak of the devil.
- Seriously.
How was it?
- I was basically flying around. Yes.
- Really?
Say hello. They're all new guests.
- Hello.
- We have four new guests.
We came today.
- Really? We came yesterday.
- Nice to meet you.
Hello, it's nice to meet you.
ALL THE GUESTS ARE HERE
Are you hungry?
- Yes, totally.
- We haven't eaten anything today.
The boss today is a bit…
Food for dinner…
He's preparing.
- It's pizza.
- Pizza?
Yes, pizza.
KIAN REHEATS THE PIZZAS
You know what? It looks good.
- It honestly does look delicious.
- Yeah.
Let's eat!
I think the food is here.
We can go get it over there.
Help me, please.
Please help me out.
Take these and bring them over there.
It's pizza!
- It looks good.
- It's pizza.
This will definitely be spicy.
You can't handle spicy food?
I am Japanese after all.
I'm not good with it either.
WORRIED IT MIGHT BE TOO SPICY
Gosh. Hey, Jun-ho.
- I'm really worried.
- I told you.
GOING DOWN TO EAT
WHILE FULL OF WORRIES
Gosh, did you make it?
Kian did it all.
I DID
TOGETHER
6:00 P.M.
We made pizza for dinner.
I made these darker ones.
Kimchi pork belly pizzas.
And the lighter ones were made by Jun-ho.
We tried our best.
I hope you like it.
WORRIED
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
What? Was it hard to explain the food?
The ones I made are spicy,
and the lighter ones are not spicy.
HIS EYES ARE BUSY CHECKING THEIR REACTIONS
It's not bad, Boss.
- It's not?
- No.
It tastes like real pizza.
- Really?
- It's soft.
- It's not bad, Boss.
- It's not?
It's amazing. The dough's good too.
Did you make the dough too?
- Yes.
He made everything himself.
How did you think of making pizza?
I was going to make kimchi jjim.
- But then I thought it'd be boring.
- Okay.
So I made pizza
with kimchi jjim ingredients as toppings.
- It's good.
- You like it?
It tastes like real pizza.
Hold on.
Why is so much of mine left?
THE BOSS'S PIZZA
Maybe they liked
the milder one more than yours.
Hey, this is bad.
What happened?
- You can't eat spicy food?
- No.
It's spicy. Too spicy.
- It's spicy because of the peppers.
- Yes.
FLICKING OFF CHEONGYANG CHILI PEPPERS
JUN-HO'S PIZZA
Cheongyang chili pepper. A bunch of it.
I guess they don't like the spicy one.
This one. Just a slice.
Try it.
But it's quite spicy.
He's terrible with spicy food.
ATTEMPT FAILS
It's okay.
- Even the mild one is spicy for him.
- The mild one?
Even the mild one's spicy?
The kimchi is a bit spicy.
EVEN KIMCHI IS SPICY FOR HIM
- Because of the kimchi?
- He can't eat it.
FEELING SOMEONE'S GAZE
You're eating Jun-ho's pizza too.
I ate two of these.
- Two slices?
- Yes. It's good.
When you made okonomiyaki,
did you feel like this too?
- I thought, "Please finish all of it."
- Right?
To see so much of it left,
it's weighing on me so much.
Oh, no.
I better eat all of the leftovers.
KIAN'S B&B
Shall we do the dishes?
IN CHARGE OF DISHWASHING
YEON-KOUNG AND ZUHA
Is it more comfortable
to talk in Japanese?
- Yes.
- Right?
- It is a bit better, right?
- Yes.
Is it tough, Kazuha?
Sorry?
Is it tough?
No.
It's not?
I'm good.
You're good?
Yes.
Want to do these by yourself?
- It's tough.
- What?
It's really tough.
Do you have things to do?
- There's a lot to do.
- Like what?
Lying down.
Okay.
How did you two meet?
I was sitting in Starbucks when I saw him.
I thought he was cute, so I talked to him.
- In Japan?
- In Japan.
Yes.
We kept in touch since then.
We became friends.
We were friends at first.
FROM FRIENDS TO A COUPLE
Who asked the other out first?
I did. I asked her to go out with me.
- It was on our fifth date.
- Fifth date?
You're manly man.
- They're in the honeymoon phase.
- They are.
Kian, when should we open the sauna?
You can enter the sauna now if you want.
You can use the sauna now.
- Now?
- Yeah.
Get changed first.
Let's put these to the side
so they can use it.
There we go.
- Okay.
It's warm.
It's so warm.
Taro, come sit here.
It's perfect.
WHILE ZUHA AND THE COUPLE ENJOY THE SAUNA
- Floorball?
- Pickle.
- Pickleball.
Shall we try it?
Should we get up and try?
THE GUESTS TRY PICKLEBALL
- You know, Seong-jun.
- Yes.
All right. Let's do it.
HOODIE STRING
AND CABBAGE BLANKET
What are the rules?
A KIAN'S B&B-STYLE NET IS SET UP
This is out, right?
Yes, this is the court.
BACK LINE
With the mat too? Gosh, it's so small.
COURT
IF YOU LET THE BALL HIT THE FLOOR,
YOU LOSE A POINT
And you have to serve behind the mat here.
- Behind the line?
- I got it.
MUST SERVE BEHIND THE LINE
Want to play one-on-one?
- First to five points.
- Okay.
- How about seven points?
Seven? I'll win anyway.
That's in.
It's out.
Didn't it touch the line?
- It didn't. Out.
- It's out.
YEON-KOUNG 0 : 1 KIAN
Hey, watch closely. Don't go easy on Boss.
Wait. The line.
You have to serve behind it.
STRICT
Out.
YEON-KOUNG 1 : 1 KIAN
- Okay.
- You didn't have to hit it.
YEON-KOUNG 2 : 1 KIAN
YEON-KOUNG 2 : 2 KIAN
Okay.
Gosh, I thought it was out.
YEON-KOUNG 3 : 2 KIAN
That went under.
YEON-KOUNG 3 : 3 KIAN
YEON-KOUNG 3 : 4 KIAN
Hey!
I can beat her.
I have a chance.
This is no joke.
Yeon-koung's getting competitive now.
Here I go, Yeon-koung.
Four to four.
YEON-KOUNG 4 : 4 KIAN
SHE SERVES TO THE CORNER
YEON-KOUNG 5 : 4 KIAN
Okay.
You should raise the net. It's too low.
Serve it safe.
Okay.
YEON-KOUNG 6 : 4 KIAN
Say I'm lousy again!
MATCH POINT
Come on. Here I go.
SHE FINISHES IT WITH A SMASH
Okay!
YEON-KOUNG WINS 7 TO 4
- What?
- Seriously.
Your competitive side kicked in.
No, it didn't.
She's not unbeatable though.
She's not that good.
TOUTING A MORAL VICTORY
This is fun.
AFTER PICKLEBALL
THEY JOIN THE SAUNA
- Thank you.
It's so hot.
- I think we can bake eggs on that.
- Right.
Should we try it?
Let's ask Mr. Kian.
- Is that possible?
- Yes.
Mr. Kian.
You know how there are
hot stones in the sauna?
Could we bake some eggs on them?
Yes, of course.
That's a great idea.
- I never thought of that.
- Seriously.
- We just leave them like this?
- It's hot.
EGGS PUT OVER HOT STONES
We can eat them tomorrow.
It takes a while.
- How do you like it?
- Me?
Your first day's almost over now.
- I'm having so much fun.
- Really?
It's so fun. For starters,
I was amazed by the door.
I loved it
because it wasn't what I expected.
I'm studying to become
an elementary school teacher.
Personally, I feel
that I'm not creative enough.
I do things by the book
and don't like
trying things outside the box.
And Mr. Kian is good
at creating new and different things
like this.
So I came here to see that,
and I think it'll be very helpful.
- Should I turn the lights off?
- Yeah.
Everyone, relax and be comfortable.
11:00 P.M.
After talking to everyone one by one,
when I looked over here,
it was like a reality dating show.
Ding-dong.
Ding-dong!
It is a reality dating show.
- Their vibes don't match Kian's B&B.
- Right.
I've never seen it before here.
What's going on?
SAME SPACE, DIFFERENT VIBE
If it's possible, we should play…
What was that game called?
Where you choose from two options…
"Would You Rather"?
- Yes.
- To see their compatibility?
All of a sudden?
Let's do it.
Fried chicken or yangnyeom chicken?
One, two, three.
- Yangnyeom.
- Fried.
They didn't match.
They're not compatible.
EXCITED FOR SOME REASON
Kian84 or Kim Yeon-koung?
SUDDENLY TURNS INTO A POPULARITY CONTEST
VERY INTRIGUED
One, two, three.
- Kim Yeon-koung.
- Kim… Yeon-koung.
That was a bit off!
Get out.
Get out!
Get out. Get out!
Did you hear that? Sorry.
You know what? I think he loves games.
I do. I love them.
OBSESSED WITH GAMES
Shall we open the karaoke room?
You sing up there. Oh, my gosh!
I suddenly feel nervous.
Does that open?
KARAOKE IS OPEN ON DAY 4
REMOTE CONTROL FOR DISCO BALL LIGHTS
DISCO BALL LIGHTS ARE ON
They come out from the ducks' eyes.
That's so nice.
Jun-ho, want to sing?
Gosh, no.
Come on, it's your last night.
- Come on.
- Tonight's your last night.
HE CHECKS OUT TOMORROW
- No.
- Tonight's your last night.
- You can do it!
What are you doing?
HE SUDDENLY WARMS UP?
I'll show you what Sunmudo is.
Here. Just briefly.
- Seriously?
- That's so cool.
In place of singing?
Okay, just a brief demonstration.
SUNMUDO DEMONSTRATION
I feel the power behind it.
He sure is a martial artist.
That's so cool.
That's it.
- That was so cool!
- Awesome.
Okay, next.
Next, Kazuha will show us ballet.
ZUHA'S BALLET TIME?
Me?
Kazuha.
- Kazuha.
- Here she comes.
- Oh, no.
- Kazuha.
Incredible.
- I'll do just a little bit.
- Okay.
Incredible.
Zuha.
- You're good. I knew it.
- Stop it.
That was great.
I almost hurt myself.
KARAOKE TIME
TALENT SHOW TIME
MASTERFUL
I've never seen that before.
Yeah, me neither.
IN THAT CASE
ANOTHER SPECIAL MOVE
TRIPLE UNDERS
That's it.
You can sing more if you want.
Just do whatever you like.
Would you like some beer?
I'll drink this instead.
- You don't drink.
- I don't drink.
How old are your children?
They're college students
in their twenties.
He has three daughters.
Three daughters? That's like my family.
- I'm the youngest.
- I see.
- It must be so hard to raise three kids.
- What?
- Isn't it hard?
- It must be.
They're all sisters,
so they play with each other.
As the dad,
don't you end up taking a back seat?
I do.
So how did you meet Sung-nam?
You said you two went to the same school,
but the age gap is quite big.
It's nothing special.
Right. It's nothing special.
I don't have any parents.
And he doesn't have any parents either.
So, we both grew up in an orphanage.
When I was presumably 5 years old,
in front of a store near the orphanage,
I was abandoned.
- I wasn't put there by my parents.
- I see.
I was found by someone as a kid
and put into the facility.
I don't know who my parents are.
So, I grew up in an orphanage.
And he also grew up in an orphanage.
So that's how you two became so close.
And that's where you met?
- That's the mentor-mentee connection?
- Yes.
That's why he's my mentor.
My homeroom teacher at the time
and Mr. Lee,
who grew up in an orphanage like me
and realized his dream
of becoming a teacher,
ended up as colleagues
at the Office of Education.
That's incredible.
So my teacher suggested I meet him,
and he introduced us.
Since then, we've been meeting often.
Their cases are similar.
Sung-nam grew up and became a teacher.
And he's also studying
to become a teacher.
But even if two people
went through similar experiences,
forming a close relationship like this
is not an easy thing.
Right.
You two must be on the same wavelength.
It must feel like
watching yourself when you were young.
Totally.
- You can relate to him.
- Yes.
I've walked the same path.
To me, the saddest thing is
he grew up too fast.
Kids should be able to act cute
and whine a bit sometimes at that age.
What was hard for me was…
I just wanted to be
the same as the other kids.
When you're young, you want to fit in.
Right.
I didn't want anyone to know about it,
so I think I hid it
and held myself back a lot.
I realized not everyone was like me.
And when I realized my situation
wasn't actually a typical one,
I thought,
"They said it was natural
to have parents."
"If so, I should have parents too."
"Then, where are mine?"
So I thought,
"If I'm not even loved by my parents,
what on earth am I?"
"Do I deserve to be loved?"
I used to be obsessed with that thought.
I think that's why I couldn't love myself
when I was young.
And as a former teacher,
he's actively working
on improving public awareness
of youths transitioning out of care.
So…
I want to do that too,
and that's how I want to live.
I want to strive to achieve
such dreams as a teacher.
He's your role model.
You're right.
I have a feeling you'll also meet
someone like yourself later.
- When you're around his age.
- I'd love that.
And you'd become
a role model to someone else.
- That'd be so cool.
- That would be ideal.
I'd be so happy.
- Kian.
- Yes?
Will you work out with us tomorrow?
- Tomorrow? At 8:10 a.m.?
- Yes.
Let's get it done quickly
in 30 to 40 minutes.
With our muscles are pumped up,
we can do some posing.
Sure.
Around 9:00 a.m. tomorrow?
Sounds great.
MORNING WORKOUT SET
Let's go to bed.
Can you help me with this?
We have to spread it out.
Pull it to that side.
UNFOLDS GIANT COMFORTER WITH GUESTS
All done.
Are you guys okay
with sharing the comforter?
- With you? Gladly.
- Yes.
It was so warm inside.
THEY'LL SLEEP UNDER ONE COMFORTER TONIGHT
Boss.
- Yeah?
- Are you sleeping together?
Yeah. But you sleep wherever you want.
Want to sleep together?
I think it'll be fun.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Like when we were kids.
- Right.
Then, you can find
a nice spot that you like.
- Kazuha.
- Yes?
Are you okay
with sleeping over there tonight?
Here?
Yeah, there.
- With everyone? Okay.
- Yeah.
If it's okay with you,
- let's sleep on that side.
- Sounds good.
You're sleeping here?
- Yes.
- Yay.
There?
- Yes, I'm here.
- I'm over here.
Is Kian sleeping here?
Come over here.
THE BOSS GETS INTO HIS SPOT AS WELL
They said to move over.
- What on earth?
- Was it Boss?
- What?
- Boss?
Taro must be so tired.
Taro, you should take off your glasses.
I have bad eyesight.
But you should take them off
when sleeping.
When you sleep…
- You're right.
- Right?
You don't see anything when you sleep.
I forgot.
But maybe you'll have dreams.
Were you getting ready to see them?
Good night.
Have a good night.
YEON-KOUNG, ZUHA, YOO-MIN, AND KOTARO
QUICKLY FALL ASLEEP
THE OTHERS GRADUALLY FALL ASLEEP TOO
SOFA, FRIDGE
TV CABINET
I think they all fell asleep.
I think so too.
Are you sleeping right away?
Could you tell us some fun stories?
GI-PYO DOESN'T WANT TO SLEEP YET
Fun stories?
Do you believe in ghosts?
Well, I do believe they might exist.
Each agency has its own ghosts.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Like urban legends?
JUN-HO'S SCARY STORY
In the old JYP building,
there was a path you took
to get to the practice room
in the basement.
- Okay.
- There was a staircase.
And everyone fell down
at the end of the stairs.
Among the trainees,
there was this young girl.
But she was the only one who didn't fall.
No one knew why we'd all get hurt there,
and we were all talking about it.
Then, that girl said,
"I know why."
"That's where a young girl
grabs onto your ankles."
What was that?
See? When you talk about ghosts…
- They're all listening.
- Exactly.
Broadcast stations
usually have a lot of ghosts.
Hey, stop it. It's scary.
- Seriously?
- You know why?
It's because the priest's gone.
But we have a Dharma Teacher.
The eggs cooked for too long.
They've all burst.
THE EGGS OVERCOOKED AND POPPED
Let's clean up
the burst eggs on the floor.
I didn't know this could happen.
The eggs overcooked and exploded.
Good work.
Let's lie down.
Get some rest. Good night.
Good night.
DAY 5
I'm ready.
7:00 A.M.
There we go.
Last time, I fell a lot,
but I didn't get hurt.
SUNG-NAM AND SEONG-JUN
SET OUT EARLY ON A TRIP
GETS UP
YEON-KOUNG PUTS ON A SOCK?
PASSES OUT AGAIN
7:45 A.M.
JUN-HO WENT BACK AND SLEPT IN HIS SPOT
BECAUSE IT WAS TOO HOT
LITTLE SOCK MERMAID IS UP
SHEDDING THE SOCK
THE GUESTS GET UP ONE BY ONE
THE BOSS IS STILL ASLEEP
8:00 A.M.
THE BOSS IS UP
Goodness. Did you sleep well?
Did you sleep well?
You snored a lot.
Gi-pyo.
- What?
- That was Gi-pyo.
- It was Gi-pyo?
- Yeah.
SNORING
GI-PYO
THE SNORING CULPRIT
- Did you sleep well?
- Yes.
Did you sleep well?
Hey, you snored a lot last night.
- I did?
- It was killing me.
- For real?
- Yeah.
EMBARRASSED
You snored a lot too.
- I snored too, right?
- Yes.
SNORING
KIAN AND GI-PYO SNORING IN HARMONY
Man, it must've been miserable
for the others.
I work out almost every day.
At least every other day.
So, I tried to work out
every day there too.
I think I used the gym the most.
- Yeon-koung's on the bike?
- Yeah.
IMPRESSED
NEXT IS LIFTING WEIGHTS
You're amazing.
What's with the sudden neck bridge?
I'm stretching.
KIAN-STYLE STRETCHING
WARM UP ENDS
YEON-KOUNG'S WORKOUT ENDS TOO
We need to work out.
Let's bring them down.
Okay.
- Let's lift weights first.
- Weights? Let's go.
I think we should do
the big muscles first.
We'll do the chest, some lateral raises,
and overhead presses together.
Then, we'll do abs.
And we'll go through three cycles.
Raises and presses?
- Yes.
- Let's do four.
Isn't three not enough? Add one more.
- We can work out the back too.
- Okay.
You'll use a towel.
You'll pull a towel in pairs.
Let's do that too.
- The back first?
- The back.
Let's begin.
You go first. One… We'll do 20.
Three, four,
five, six, seven.
Two, three.
GRIMACING
Five, six.
Go straight into push-ups.
MOVING ALONG TO JUN-HO'S COUNT
Four, five, six, seven, eight.
Why are you going so fast?
OFFBEAT
Fourteen, fifteen.
SHOULDER WORKOUT WHILE GRIMACING
Five, six,
seven, eight.
Go straight into overhead presses.
Three, four.
AB EXERCISE
25 REPS
Ready, set, go.
One, two.
- Three.
- Come on.
- Four.
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Where are you pushing them?
IN A STRAIGHT LINE
EVEN STIMULATION OF ABS
BY CHANGING DIRECTIONS
- What do you mean?
- Where are you pushing them?
You know.
They're supposed to go back and forth.
Ten. Five more.
One, two.
Three. Harder!
Four.
FINISHED
All done.
Okay, let's see.
Are you ready?
Darn it, it's my turn.
Come on. Let's go.
All right. One, two.
Three, four.
HE'S NOT GOING EASY ON HIM
Seven, eight,
nine.
Two, three.
Four, five.
FINISHED
Five more!
Five. Five more!
- One, two.
- What?
BIG PAYBACK
Five more.
Five more! One.
HE'S DONE OVER 40 REPS
SATISFIED
Five. Very nice.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
I'm so tired.
That felt like cardio.
Shall we do some posing?
Together?
Are you going to show off your bodies?
GI-PYO AND JIN-AN
DID BODYBUILDING IN COLLEGE
- Then, show us.
- Show us.
His back looks great.
BULGING
Their bodies look great as hell.
CAN'T TAKE HIS EYES OFF THEM
The light's good over there.
Right, there's sunlight.
WELL-LIT AREA
I should try to learn about it.
TAKES OFF
- Are you joining us?
- Yeah.
I'll give it a try.
Good.
THE BOSS JOINS THEM
- Not bad, right?
- You look great.
- Not bad?
- Yes.
BODYBUILDING POSES WITH KIAN
FIRST POSE
FRONT DOUBLE BICEPS
Gosh, it's big.
WAKING THE MUSCLES
GLANCING
My lats don't show.
EXEMPLARY POSE
Raise your chest.
- Raise it?
- Yes, that's it.
You have nice biceps.
BICEPS
WAKE UP, MY MUSCLES
Looking good.
SECOND POSE
FRONT LAT SPREAD
Lift up the back of your hands.
- You're pretty fit.
- Not bad?
Yeah.
HE SEES SOMETHING
Wait. Let me pull this hair out.
INCREDULOUS
Wait.
THE BIZARRE KIAN
FRONT-ROW SEAT
I did it. I got it out.
"Let me pull this hair out"!
- We'll show the back now.
- Okay.
ONTO THE NEXT POSE
AFTER PLUCKING THE HAIR
Contract your back muscles first.
THIRD POSE
BACK DOUBLE BICEPS
- Jun-ho, does it look okay?
- It looks good.
I'm squeezing everything.
SQUEEZING HIS MUSCLES
AND HIS FACE
TREMBLING
- Not too shabby.
- Great!
Not too shabby.
Not too shabby!
You're going to get a cramp.
And this.
FOURTH POSE
SIDE CHEST
Bend your knees a bit.
SEDUCTIVE
This pose was cool.
It's the best one.
You have to put your toes
in the middle of your other foot.
Like this?
Place the toes there.
A kind smile is crucial.
JIN-AN AND GI-PYO ARE PERFECT
EMBARRASSED FOR HIM
FULL OF CONFIDENCE
- Good work, everyone.
- Good work.
Morning workouts are so nice.
EGGS BAKED IN THE SAUNA
Thank you.
EATING PROTEIN AFTER WORKING OUT
They smell just like the jjimjilbang ones.
- They do?
- Yes.
You're right.
TAKES A BITE
How is it?
These ones were cooked well.
- They're savory.
- Right.
- Taro, let's go.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- What?
- Have a nice trip.
- Okay.
Yes, I'm finished. Have a good time.
- Thank you.
- Take care and see you later.
Bye.
Our friendship will last forever.
Thank you for everything.
See you later.
THE COUPLE AND LUGE TEAM GO OUT
This is nice.
I should pack.
10:00 A.M.
GUEST JUN-HO PACKS HIS BAGS
AFTER HAVING THE LONGEST STAY
- Jun-ho Two.
- Yes?
Have you eaten?
- I haven't.
- Want me to fix you something?
There's still time.
- It's okay.
- I'll make you food.
You're leaving soon.
Are you sure? Thank you then.
Jun-ho Two, do you want some nurungji?
I'd like that.
Let's put all of it in.
There's a lot of people here.
Yeon-koung's making nurungji.
- Breakfast?
- Yeah.
THE BOSS GOES TO THE KITCHEN TOO
We can just eat
chicken and kimchi with rice.
That sounds delicious.
There's leftover pizza too.
- Pizza?
- Two slices.
Here's the leftover pizza from yesterday.
THE FOOD THAT WEIGHED ON THE BOSS'S MIND
I should finish the pizza.
EATS IT RIGHT AWAY TO RID OF HIS BURDEN
- Kian, have some.
- I will.
- Want more?
- Yes.
Gosh, Jun-ho Two is leaving now.
Yes.
We've been so grateful.
You treated me like a friend
who came to hang out at your place.
You made me feel like your brother
or your friend.
I had a blast.
And I got to eat with the staff.
That was what Boss wanted.
Like you were visiting a friend's place.
And so, when Smita and all of us
danced together then,
it became a reality.
It was like we were very close friends.
While all of us talked
and had fun together,
we became best friends.
- Happy Birthday, dear Jun-ho
I became best friends with a priest too.
I made many good friends here.
- Right.
- For sure.
- I'm glad to hear that.
- Right?
DHARMA TEACHER HYEONUNG, LEE JUN-HO
IT WAS SHORT BUT WE MADE DEEP CONNECTIONS
Mr. Kian, there's something
I wanted to give you.
This is a singing bowl
I've used for a long time.
- Isn't it precious to you?
- Yes.
WATER OFFERING BOWL
SINGING BOWL
- Thank you so much.
- Sure.
Always think carefully.
And whenever you feel stuck,
give it a hit.
I've only been taking things from you.
- No, not at all.
- And you're my guest.
I had a great time.
Thank you very much.
GAINS ANOTHER CHERISHED POSSESSION
Checking out?
I wish you all good health and peace.
- I'll see you again one day.
- Sure.
- Thank you.
I'll get going then.
- Take care.
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
- Good luck!
- Thank you.
Kian's B&B is "pollock."
You see,
nothing goes to waste with pollock.
Kian's B&B is just like that.
The weather's so nice.
GUEST JUN-HO CHECKS OUT
Gosh, he's gone.
We should dust off this giant comforter.
Let's do that then.
All right. This is so big though.
Hey, how do we…
It's way too big.
Let's each pull it back further.
We should bunch up the edges a bit.
- Or it'll drag on the ground.
- Right.
Okay.
Got it, right?
Hold onto the middle, everyone.
We have to hold on like this.
Hold on with two hands.
Don't let it drag from here.
CAREFUL
Hold it high.
This is all about teamwork. Focus!
Pull.
Don't let it touch the ground.
- Come this way.
- Hey, be careful.
It's muddy over there.
Come here. Pull this way.
- Careful.
- Yeah, right there.
- Kian, you'll slip.
- Don't get close.
Okay, we'll shake it
up and down ten times.
Ready, set, go.
- One.
- Two.
SHAKING COMFORTER ALONG TO THE COUNT
Five, six, seven, eight.
WHY IS IT FLAPPING?
Pull!
Spread out.
THE ONLY ONE JUMPING UP AND DOWN
- Six, seven.
- Spread out.
Eight, nine, ten.
Hold on. Let's take a break.
Gosh, the dust.
BLOCKING THE DUST OUT
I think the dust
is collecting in the center.
- Exactly.
- Jun-ho, hold it like this with one hand.
- Boss, hold it like this.
- What?
Look.
Hold the middle like this
so it doesn't sag.
- Here we go.
- Ready, set, go.
ONE MORE TIME
JUMPS AROUND AGAIN AFTER CHANGING STANCE
Boss isn't doing it right.
Five, six…
Eight, nine…
Why are you flapping around so much?
Shake along to the count!
But you didn't count!
God, this is tiring.
Why are you ignoring the count
and flapping around on your own?
You looked like a fairy
who was about to fly away.
- She said you looked like a fairy.
- A fairy? I did?
Fairies are cute.
Now, let's fold it up.
This way? Like this?
- Pull both ends there.
- That's right.
Meet in the middle.
Now go back,
and let's meet in the middle again.
In the middle.
We've folded it so many times.
Could there be
a bigger comforter in Korea?
- No way.
- We have to put it away.
One, two, three.
All done.
THEY DISPERSE AND START CLEANING
EVERY CORNER
Gosh, it's so dusty here.
It's so dirty today.
Goodness.
Gosh, I keep saying "goodness."
It really is dirty.
There's so much to clean.
Zuha's doing well.
She works hard.
We're just cleaning all day.
We're cleaning properly today.
I think we're pretty much done.
It looks clean.
ALPENSIA SKI JUMPING CENTER
GI-PYO, JIN-AN, YOUNG-HYUN
Man, it's huge.
ALPENSIA SKI JUMPING CENTER
ABOUT A 93-M-TALL
SKI JUMP TOWER
I can't believe we're sledding here.
I never imagined it.
SLEDDING ON A SKI JUMP RAMP
The slope feels different this way.
Where did Taro go?
SONGJEONGHAEBYEON BEACH
KOTARO, YOO-MIN
It's the sea!
Gosh, this is so moving.
SONGJEONGHAEBYEON BEACH
It's so pretty.
Yoo-min, be careful!
Let's see who can find the cuter shell.
Two shells?
Okay. Decision time!
One, two!
Ta-da!
Taro.
What a cool picture!
You look so pretty.
This is so nice.
BONGPYEONG
SUNG-NAM, SEONG-JUN
- It's the memorial hall?
- Yeah.
LEE HYOSEOK MEMORIAL HALL
"When Buckwheat Flowers Bloom."
Did you read this in school too?
- This short story?
- Of course.
Where did he get such inspiration from?
LEE HYOSEOK'S BIRTHPLACE
They'd make these back in the day.
NATIONAL MUSEUM
OF THE ANNALS OF THE JOSEON DYNASTY
A TOUR FULL OF PASSION FOR LEARNING
It was returned after 100 years.
It was built in 1606?
"Bangsangsi."
- We're checking out tomorrow.
- Right.
It feels so short.
What a shame.
AT LAST DESTINATION
WITH BITTERSWEET FEELINGS
Family photos.
- Hello.
- We'd like to take a photo.
- Sure.
- Like this?
My skin looks fairer too.
It looks good. It came out well.
I've wanted to do this since 10th grade.
- I see.
- Yes.
I must be getting old. I'm tearing up.
2:00 P.M.
What's that? Did you write down plans?
There are just a few days left.
I'm going to plan them like this.
That's cool.
How many nights are there?
One, two, three.
- Four nights.
- There are four nights left.
It can be about the plan, new ideas,
or anything you want to change.
Any opinions?
- First, for today…
- Yes?
I have to go to the market.
YEON-KOUNG IS TODAY'S CHEF
You're making pasta, right?
Pasta and chicken breast naengchae salad?
I'll help you when you cook.
About the karaoke room,
I think it's better to open it
the night before someone checks out.
Tonight's the last night
for three of them.
And the other four.
- They all leave.
- What?
They all leave tomorrow.
ALL OF THE GUESTS CHECK OUT TOMORROW
- Right.
- Three-day stays.
THE KARAOKE ROOM WILL OPEN TONIGHT
- But I think…
- Yeah?
It feels like
we always have dinner.
Then, we either wash up or use the sauna.
And then, we have a drink,
and that's how it usually goes.
I do think it'd be nice to let them
drink during dinner if they want.
You know what, Yeon-koung?
How about we give that a try today?
GIVE WHAT A TRY?
- Serve everything like a buffet.
- Okay.
And let them on their own…
Including beverages and alcohol?
Yeah, and let them eat
like a wedding buffet.
- They can drink too.
- That's not a bad idea.
- Like a party?
- Yeah.
You know, like going around
drinking and mingling.
We'll make it feel like a party.
Right, it has to feel like a party.
What should we call it?
- "Happy Kian's B&B Day"?
- That's good.
But what do you do at a party?
- Like usually?
- You usually dress up.
As if you're the most stylish person ever.
Right.
Get dressed up for tonight then.
You have to dress up too.
- Me?
- You can finally wear that suit.
I thought I'd never be able to
wear it again here.
- Finally.
- You have to wear it.
That's some good news.
But will there be enough time?
- It'll be tight.
- Right?
Or while we cook, you and Zuha can…
- Set up?
- We could do it then.
Spruce the place up.
- Good idea, right?
- Yeah.
I guess this is why we need meetings.
SATISFIED
Let's go out and buy groceries.
Okay, let's go.
Let's buy them quickly.
We have to buy beer and soju.
CANNED DRINKS FOR THE PARTY
Cans.
We'll take that cake. Yes, thank you.
- We're here.
- Let's go.
- Here we go.
- All right.
HURRYING BACK HOME
We picked a good cake.
- It gives off party vibes.
- Right.
DEALING WITH THE DOOR FOR THE FIFTH DAY
I'm so tired.
- Why won't it open?
- It's open.
It's open.
Go in.
I had no energy to jump.
Isn't it so funny?
- About time you got a call, right?
- Right.
3:30 P.M.
I guess no one's checking in today.
- We're not getting any calls.
- No.
WITHOUT NEW GUESTS CHECKING IN
THEY START PREPPING FOR THE PARTY
- We have to cook, right?
- Yes.
I'll assist you.
TODAY'S SOUS-CHEF AND MAIN CHEF
What will you do first?
I'm going to boil chicken first.
It takes the longest.
Put all the chicken in at once?
- You know the amount. I don't know.
- Just put them in?
CHICKEN BREAST FOR SALAD
There are 11 people.
- So this much for now?
- Sure.
IN CHARGE OF DECORATION
Hey, just put the beer…
Here? Or outside to chill them?
- Let's just put them outside.
- Okay.
Okay.
- All done.
- That's it.
You can go back in, Zuha.
DRINKS PUT OUTSIDE TO CHILL
I'll do it.
- Boss.
- Yeah?
We're getting rid of this, right?
- What?
- The mat here.
- We have to fold it up.
- Fold it?
- You're going to do it alone?
- I don't know.
It won't be easy.
1ST PREPARATION FOR HAPPY KIAN'S B&B DAY
FOLD THE MAT
THE MAT THAT ZUHA WILL FOLD BY HERSELF IS…
ABOUT AS BIG AS 44 ZUHAS
AND WEIGHS ABOUT 200 KG
FOLDS THE CORNER
Lift it here.
And fold this.
LET'S GO BACK
IT'S NOT EASY
5 MINUTES SPENT ON ONE SIDE
Are you okay?
THE MAT CAN'T BE PULLED
IT PUSHES ZUHA BACK
- You're doing well.
- Right?
AND THE ONE LAUGHING
- Fold it.
- But am I doing it right?
- Does it fold in half?
- You figure it out.
ANNOYED
Just pull and fold it up.
You're doing well.
GLARING
You say it like it's easy,
but it's so hard.
It's unfolding over there.
I can't do this.
How am I supposed to do this by myself?
I mean, from upstairs,
standing like this,
he said, "You figure it out."
I guess it's that kind of place.
You have to handle things by yourself.
KIAN'S PHILOSOPHY
HANDLE IT YOURSELF
FIGURING OUT BY HERSELF
This is crazy.
SHE SEES KIAN FROM BEHIND
What was that?
SENSING MURDEROUS INTENT
Sorry? What?
PLAYING DUMB
WHILE AT LEAST HALF AS BEEN FOLDED
HE STRUGGLES TO FIND SUPPLIES
Why is it so bare-bones?
AFTER INVENTORY CHECK,
HE RETURNS EMPTY-HANDED
Zuha, you were doing it alone? I'm sorry.
- Why weren't you helping?
- Sorry.
I thought you were bringing in a table.
I looked for it, but there was no table.
- Really?
- Here.
One, two, three.
Geez, what is up with this?
This may be several hundred kilograms.
How did you do this by yourself?
Gosh, many things happened.
One, two, three.
- Is this right?
- It is.
AFTER STRUGGLES, SHE FOLDS IT
Maybe we should just push it to that side.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Yes.
- Pull the bottom.
- Wait.
Yes, right there.
She took off her socks.
Yeah, I'll pull and you push.
One, two, three.
PUSHES ON IN BARE FEET
Now, the other side.
Isn't the floor all burned though?
It is.
WELL-COOKED FLOOR
Every house in the countryside
used to have floors like this. It's okay.
- They look like a loaves of bread.
- You're right.
They are loaves of bread.
All right. That will do.
PARTY SPACE SECURED
- Your feet look cooked.
- Right?
BROWN AT THE WARMEST SPOTS
It's that hot.
No, if we open the window for a bit,
it'll be okay.
It's because we kept the mat on.
- That's why, right?
- Yeah.
- Geez.
- Look at this.
- The floor.
- It got a proper burn.
- It definitely did.
- Yeah.
- Is it okay?
- No wonder why it was so hot.
So how do you want to do it?
Like an awards show?
That'd be the best choice.
Make it like an awards show?
Yeah, like the Baeksang Arts Awards.
This is the stage then?
I think three tables would be perfect.
- Put tables here?
- Three tables.
There, there, and there.
And the stage would be up there.
And as they enjoy the party…
With chairs too?
We'll say,
"Everyone, we'll begin the party."
"Are you guys enjoying your last night?"
Something like that.
Okay, we'll give it a try.
LET'S DO IT AWARDS SHOW-STYLE
You know the tables outside?
Let's clean them and bring them in.
- In the outdoor tent?
- You know. Yeah.
Outside.
Okay.
2ND PREPARATION
GET TABLES AND CHAIRS
We're trying to turn
Boss's imagination into reality.
But it's so hard.
But to be honest,
you can't figure him out, can you?
CAN'T FOLLOW HIS THOUGHTS
I think he'll be satisfied
if there are tables.
I think so too.
Let's do it like the Baeksang Arts Awards.
TO MAKE HIS IMAGINATION A REALITY
THEY SEARCH STORAGE FIRST
- Look at this.
- Are those the chairs?
But you think these will do?
CHAIRS THEY NEED TO TAKE
Then, let's bring the whole box and…
Use that as a table?
A BLUE BOX FOR A TABLE
I heard there are wine glasses here.
Here they are.
Let's bring them.
Let's go.
I'll put them here for now.
THEY RAID STORAGE FIRST
- Let's bring one table first.
- Okay.
- And all the chairs?
- Yes. We'll take this.
OUTDOOR TENT IS NEXT
Just like that.
THEY TAKE THE CAMPING TABLE AND CHAIRS TOO
- What on earth?
- What?
- Are there cows?
- Yeah, look.
THEY SEE COWS UPON RETURN
Gosh.
Are they milk cows?
BRIEF PAUSE TO WATCH COWS
That must be the mother cow.
I think it's the big black one.
She saw us.
- Our eyes met.
- Right.
Not scared?
- I think it's okay.
- Really?
- No, I meant you.
- Me? I'm fine.
I like animals.
- You do?
- Yes.
She's coming.
She's coming over here.
- Does she want to fight?
- Right?
- You should…
- Do something.
You stay back a bit.
I think I'll lose.
Which animal is your favorite?
- Dogs.
- Dogs?
She's very different from a dog.
A "DOG" AT KIAN'S B&B
HE CALLS HER
It's all right.
- Just once…
- Is it okay?
Be careful.
- Zuha, now's the time.
- Be careful.
Now's the time.
There you go.
Right now.
Wait! Hey, not this!
- No, they're glasses!
- It was so hard to find these!
If you hold this, she'll come to you.
- No!
- Bye.
- Sorry.
- Hey, watch out for poop.
- She's coming!
- Come on!
- It's because of this.
- Hurry up.
Let's hurry.
- She's coming.
- Hurry up.
No, we have to leave the box behind.
What are you talking about? Hurry up!
Run faster, Zuha.
- Geez, what are we doing?
- Gosh, there it is.
- Sorry!
- Bye.
HURRIEDLY SAYS GOODBYE
- You can just bring the chairs.
- Okay.
Will I be able to carry all of them?
Can you carry all of them?
STRONG ZUHA
Okay, good.
- It's better than making multiple trips.
- Right.
Nice, you're doing well.
Watch your step.
STUMBLES
What is it?
- What is it?
- Darn it, I stepped on poop!
I stepped on poop!
You didn't just step on it.
You rubbed it in, Zuha.
KIAN'S BIZARRE B&B SEASON 2
Subtitle translation by: Wayne Ryu